var questions = [
	{
		question:"You get called by the nursing home to treat a UTI in a 88 year old male. At which creatinine clerance should we avoid using nitrofurantoin?",
		answer:"CrCl &lt; 60"
	},
	{
		question:"Name the blood test used to help diagnose Primary Biliary Cirrhosis",
		answer:"Anti-Mitochondrial Antibody"
	},
	{
		question:"Name the two classes of medications used to treat BPH",
		answer:"<ol><li>Alpha Adrenergic Blockers</li><li>5-&alpha; Reductase Inhibitors</li></ol>"
	},
	{
		question:"Describe Bell's Phenomenon",
		answer:"An upward gaze with an inability to close the eyelid on the affected side"
	},
	{
		question:"Convert Hydromorph Contin 12 mg po bid to Hydromorph S/C q4h",
		answer:"2mg s/c q4h"
	},
	{
		question:"What blood test is the best for helping diagnose Celiac Disease?",
		answer:"IgA Anti-TTG (Tissue Trans-Glutaminase)"
	},
	{
		question:"Name Charcot's Triad for Acute Cholangitis",
		answer:"<ol><li>Fever</li><li>Right Upper Quadrant Pain</li><li>Jaundice</li></ol>"
	},
	{
		question:"What condition should you consider if an elderly patient describes a unilateral sensorineural hearing loss and/or tinnitus?",
		answer:"Acoustic Neuroma<br>(also known as a Vestibular Schwannoma)"
	},
	{
		question:"Which class of medications should be avoided in Lewy-Body Dementia?",
		answer:"Anti-psychotics"
	},
	{
		question:"Name 3 different ways to diagnose an <i>H. pylori</i> infection",
		answer:"<ol><li><i>H. pylori</i> serology</li><li>Urea Breath Test</li><li>Endoscopic Biopsy</li></ol>"
	}
];